Can't get the monkey off your back?
无法摆脱工作的压力？
Then put it in your mouth...
那就来一杯…
... with Monkeyshine Beer!
…猴子乐啤酒吧
Get it,monkey
喝一口猴子乐
Get it,get it,monkey
Monkey,monkey
猴子乐…
Monkeyshine Beer.
猴子乐啤酒
Because it's a jungle out there!
因为外面是一片丛林
That commercial always makes me so sad.
那个广告总是让我悲从中来
But then the guy opens his beer and girls run at him...
但是那个砘镆豢啤酒 女人就拥上来了…
...so everything works out okay.
…所以最后一切还好的
I meant because the monkey reminds me of Marcel.
我的意思是 那只猴子让我想到了马赛
I can see that.
我看得出来
Because they both have those big brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
它们都有棕色的大眼睛 还有鼓鼓的小下巴
And the fact that they're both monkeys?
而且它们都是猴子
I wonder if I did the right thing, giving him away.
有时候我怀疑我是不是做错了 不应该把它送走
Ross,you had to. He was humping everything in sight.
你是不得已的啊 看到什么东西都要上
My Malibu Barbie will no longer be wearing white to her wedding.
我的马里布芭比娃娃 结婚不能穿纯洁的白纱了
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
记得有时它会跟你们借帽子…
...and when you got it back, there'd be monkey raisins in it?
…等你要回来的时候里面会有 小小的猴子“葡萄干”？
When he did it,it was funny. When I did it to my boss's hat....
它干的就叫好玩 如果我对我老板这么做的话…
Suddenly,I had this big "attitude problem."
突然就变成了我的态度不好
The One With the Super Bowl,Part 1
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第12集 超级杯后（第一集）
Hey,check it out! Guess what I got?
你们看，猜我有什么？
Rhythm?
韵律感，对不对？
No. My first fan mail!
不是，第一封影迷信
"Dear Dr. Ramoray:
亲爱的雷医生：
I love you and would do anything to have you."
我爱你，为了得到你 我可以不惜一切
My gosh! "Your not-so-secret admirer,Erika Ford."
“你不神秘的仰慕者 方艾丽”
Oh,wait.
等一下
"P.S. Enclosed,please find 14 of my eyelashes."
：“附注：随函附上了 我十四根的睫毛”
In Crazy World,that means you're married.
在疯子的世界里 那就表示你结婚了
It's not addressed to Days Of Our Lives. This came to your apartment.
这不是寄到制作单位的 这是直接送到你家去
She was in our building.
她去过我们的大楼
Oh,my God.
我的天啊
I got my very own stalker!
我有我自己的变态影迷了
Where are you off to?
你上哪儿去了？
There's a paleontology conference in L.A.
因为洛杉矶 有一个古生物学研讨会
So I figured I'd go and drive down to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
我会去，然后开车到动物园 给马赛一个惊喜
He will be surprised. Till he realizes he's a monkey...
我想它会很惊喜的 直到它发现它是猴子…
...and isn't capable of that emotion.
…它根本就没办法有那种情绪
Phoebe? That really cute guy is here again.
菲比，那个可爱的砘镉掷戳
Okay,so everyone...
各位…
... pretend I'm telling you a story and it's really funny.
…假装我在讲故事给你们听 故事非常的好笑
So everyone just laugh. Now!
所以大家要笑
I know,I know!
我知道
I'm Rob Donan.
我叫罗伯杜南
Hi,Rob Donan.
罗伯杜南
I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really great.
我对音乐一窍不通 不过我觉得你非常棒
Anyway,I schedule performers for children's libraries.
我在替市里的儿童图书馆 安排艺人的演出
And I was thinking,have you thought about playing your songs for kids?
我在想，你有没有想过 为小孩子演唱你的歌呢？
I would love to have kids...
我好想要小孩哦…
...hear me play the songs that I will write for them.
听我…听我演唱 我为他们写的歌
What do we do for dinner?
你今天晚饭做什么？
We could cook for ourselves.
我们可以留在家里吃自己啊
It's Erika.
我是艾丽
My God. The stalker!
变态影迷
Never mind. It's open.
没关系，门没关
Hitting her with a frying pan is a good idea.
对，用平底锅打她是个好主意
But we want a backup plan, just in case she isn't a cartoon!
不过，我们应该想点别的 以防她不是卡通人物
Let's get out of here!
离开这里
The one time they're not home!
偏挑这个时候不在
We'll leave. When we pass her...
我们走时 在楼梯上碰到的时候…
...she won't know me, because we never met!
…她不会知道是我 因为我们没有见过啊
That's how radio stars escape stalkers!
那是收音机明星的方法
She's coming!
她来了
It's me.
是我
This is it. This is how we're gonna die.
就这样了，我们就这样死的
You ready?
预备好了？
Wait,wait,wait!
等等…
Erika!
艾丽
-Mr. Geller? -Yes,hi.
盖勒先生？ 是，嗨
Dean Lipson,zoo administrator.
黎迪恩，我是这里的行政组长
You had a question?
听说你有个问题，是不是？
I can't find the monkey I donated last year. He's a capuchin...
我似乎找不到我去年捐的猴子 它是一只戴帽猿…
...answers to the name Marcel?
…它的名字叫做马赛？
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
我恐怕有个坏消息要告诉你
Marcel has passed on.
马赛它已经过世了
Oh,my God. What happened?
天哪，怎么会呢？
He got sick, and then he got sicker...
它生病了，然后它病得很重…
...and then he got a little better.
…然后它突然好了一点
But then he died.
然后就死了
I can't believe this!
我真不敢相信
I'm sorry,Mr. Geller. But you know,there's an old saying:
很抱歉，盖勒先生 你也知道嘛，俗话说：
"Sometimes monkeys die."
“猴子难免一死”
It's not a great saying...
不是很好的俗语…
... but it certainly is fitting today.
…用在今天却很帖切
-Someone should've called me. -I'm sorry.
那应该有人通知我才对呀 对不起
Look,I know this can't bring him back...
我知道这不能够让它复活…
... but here,it's just a gesture.
…这是我一点心意，请收下
Zoo dollars?
动物园礼券？
Yes,and come see the bird show at 4. The macaws wear hats.
对，四点请过来看一看鸟秀 金刚鹦鹉戴帽子
It's a lot cuter if your monkey hasn't just died.
你的猴子没死的话会可爱多了
I know.
我知道
I can't believe Joey's having lunch with his stalker!
真不敢相信 乔伊去跟他的变态影迷吃饭
What is she like?
她长得怎么样？
You remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
你还记得“战栗游戏” 里面的凯西贝兹？
Well,she looks the exact opposite of that.
她长得跟她完全相反
And she's not crazy?
那她不是疯子吗？
Oh,no,no. She's a total whack-job.
不，她的完全秀斗了
She thinks that Joey is actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
她以为乔伊真的是雷崔克医生
Oh,my God!
我的天哪
And he's going out with her?
然后他还要去跟她约会？
He cannot pursue this.
他不能这么做的
Just because this woman sees Joey through the magical box...
就因为这个女人以为她可以 在她的客厅黑盒里面看乔伊…
...in her living room doesn't mean she's not a person.
…并不表示她就不是人啊
Does she not deserve happiness? Does she not deserve love?
我是说，她应该得到快乐 也应该得到爱呀
Why are you looking at me? He's the one who wants to boff the maniac!
你们看我干什么？ 想上那个疯子的是乔伊耶
Are you okay?
你还好吧？
No. I'm just nervous.
不，我只是很紧张
Maybe if I just picture them all in their underwear....
如果我幻想他们只穿内衣…
That's not a good idea. That's the reason the last guy got fired.
不，那个主意不好 上个砘锞褪悄茄被开除的
I'm used to playing for grownups.
我只是…我习惯为大人演唱
Grownups drink their coffee and do their grownup thing.
大人只是… 边喝咖啡边做他们大人做的事
And kids...
小孩呢…
...Iisten.
…会专心听
It's just a huge responsibility.
我觉得这个责任好重大
What?
怎么了？
Are you gonna kiss me?
你要亲我吗？
I was thinking about it.
我正在考虑
Alrighty! Let's play some tunes!
那好，好耶，咱们来些音乐
-Hi,everybody. I'm Phoebe. -Hi,Phoebe!
各位，我是菲比 菲比
I'm gonna play some songs about grandparents,okay?
现在我要唱一首 关于祖父母的歌
Now Grandma's a person Who everyone likes
奶奶走到哪里都大受欢迎
She bought you a train And a bright shiny bike
她送你火车跟一辆簇新单车
But lately she hasn't Been coming to dinner
但最近她不再来共进晚餐
And last time you saw her She looked so much thinner
上回你看到她时 她看起来瘦多了
Now your mom and your dad said She moved to Peru
你妈跟你爸说她搬去秘鲁
But the truth is she died And someday you will too
事实上她死了，有一天你也会
-Oh,Drake,isn't it amazing? -Yeah,it is.
崔克，这真是太好了 是啊，没错
What?
怎么了？
Well,here we sit,devil-may-care...
现在我们轻松地坐在这儿…
...and a while ago you were reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
…但不久前 你还在重注西蒙的脊髓
That was a tricky one.
是啊，那实在不简单
In reality...
事实上…
...that operation takes 10 hours. But they only showed it for 2 minutes.
…那个手术要花上十几个钟头 可是他们只播了两分钟而已
Who's "they"?
“他们”是谁？
No one.
没有啦
Drake,you are so talented. Let me see those hands.
崔克，你真有才华 让我看看那双手
Oh,these hands, these beautiful hands.
这双美丽的手
I could just eat them.
真想吃掉它们
But I won't.
但我不会
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
不然我的手表一定会掉下来
No,seriously.
不，说真的，这双手…
These hands...
这双…
...these miracle,magical, life-giving hands.
…救人无数，创造奇迹的手
Just to be near them,touch them, maybe even lick one?
只要靠近，抚摸 或许甚至舔一只就好了
All right. Just one.
好吧，一只就好了
You're good at that.
你很行耶
Oh,my God! Someone! He's choking!
天哪，来人哪，他噎住了
Is anyone here a doctor?
这里有没有医生？
Yes,the best doctor in Salem!
沙仑市最好的医生就在这儿
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
雷崔克医生
Meet me in the nocturnal house in 15 minutes.
你十五分钟之后到夜行馆等我
Hey,look. I don't really enjoy being with other men that way.
少来了 我不喜欢跟别的男人那样
But,zoo dollars?
要动物园礼券吗？
It's about your monkey!
我要告诉你有关你猴子的事
It's alive.
它还没死
I don't understand. Why didn't you help that man?
我不懂，你为什么不救他？
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
因为我是神经外科医生…
...and that was clearly a case of...
…他显然是患了…
... "foodal chokage."
…“食道阻塞症”
I gotta tell you something
好吧，听着 我要坦白一件事…
You don't have to tell me anything.
你什么都不用告诉我
You don't have to explain yourself to me.
你不用向我解释什么
Who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Ramoray?
我算老几啊 竟然敢怀疑伟大的雷医生
I should be happy to be near you.
能接近你，我就该满足了
Hey,l
嘿，我…
Hey what?
嘿什么？
That's it. Just hey!
就那样，只是嘿
Like at the end of a dance. Hey!
像结束了一首舞那样，嘿！
There'll be times when you get older
有一天你们会长大
When you'll want to sleep with people
你们会想跟别人上床
Just to make them like you But don't!
只为搏得他们欢心 但不要这么做
'Cause...
因为…
... that's another thing...
…那是另一件…
... that you don't wanna do Everybody!
…你不要做的事 一起来
That's another thing That you don't wanna do
那是另一件你不要做的事
-Excellent! -Very informative!
太棒了 很有教育性
Not at all inappropriate!
一点也不会不恰当
Thank you for coming,everybody! There are cookies in the back.
谢谢各位光临 后面有饼干要送给你们
That was great.
真是棒透了
The kids loved you.
孩子们爱死你了
Yea! I rock!
对呀，我酷毙了
And you know why? Because you told the truth.
你知道为什么吗？ 因为你说实话
Nobody ever tells kids the truth.
从来没有人对小孩子说实话
You were incredible!
你真是了得
But...?
但…？
-How'd you know there was a "but"? -I sense these things.
你怎么知道还有“但…”？ 这种事情逃不过我的
It was either "but" or "butter."
不是“但是”就是“蛋饼”
The thing is,I think some of the parents...
我想问题是有些父母…
...they were hoping that...
…会希望你多唱一点…
...you'd play more songs about barnyard animals.
…农场动物那类的歌曲
I can do that.
这个我办得到啊
Really?
真的？
Because that would be fantastic!
因为那样子会非常棒
What? You wanna kiss me?
怎么？你要亲我吗？
I'm thinking about it.
我正在考虑
The bat.
蝙蝠
Ambassador of darkness.
黑暗世界的大使
Flitting out of his cave like a winged messenger.
像一只插翅的信差 冲出了巢穴
Sightless specter of the macabre.
死神之舞的盲目幽灵
Buddy,my monkey?
兄弟，我的猴子呢？
Oh,yeah,right.
对了…
There was a break-in...
在几个月前…
...a few months back. Inside job.
…这里被洗劫，内贼干的
Your monkey was taken.
你的猴子被偷了
The zoo told me that my monkey was dead!
我的天哪 可是动物园说我的猴子死了
The zoo!
动物园
You believe everything the zoo tells you?
你相信 动物园说的每一件事吗？
That's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.
动物园只是告诉过我这件事
Of course they'll say that! They don't want the bad publicity.
他们当然会说它死了 他们害怕消息传出去会不好看
It's all a great big cover-up.
他们掩饰得密不透风
Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?
你知道这件事情 牵涉到多高层吗？
That guy Lipson?
那个黎先生？
Lipson knows?
黎先生知道？
Lipson knows,huh?
黎先生知道，是吗？
Hello,Mr. Possum.
哈罗，负子鼠先生
Enigma of the trees, upside-down denizen of the night.
树上的谜团 上下颠倒的夜之民
-Taunting gravity -Buddy,my monkey. My monkey?
正在嘲弄着地心引力… 兄弟，我的猴子呢？
Word on the street
道上的传闻…
When I say "street," I mean those pretend streets here at the zoo.
当我说“道上”的时候 我指的是园里的游园道路
Of course.
当然了
Your monkey found a new career...
你的猴子有了新职业了…
...in the entertainment field. That's all I know.
…往娱乐界发展去了 我只知道这一些
This is unbelievable!
真是令人难以置信
So what is this information worth to you,my friend?
好了，这个消息 对你值多少钱啊，朋友？
Are you trying to get me to bribe you?
你是暗示我要贿赂你吗？
Maybe.
或许吧
But you already told me everything.
可是你都已经告诉我了
Check it out.
你们看
He actually is the Monkeyshine monkey!
马赛就是 啤酒乐广告里的那只猴子
What'll you do?
那你打算怎么办？
I'm gonna call the beer company and try to find him.
我要打电话给那家啤酒厂 问他们它在哪里啊
That's what I did when I lost my Clydesdales.
我丢了马儿时就是这么做的
Okay,hi again!
你们好
Hi,Phoebe!
菲比好
Today,we're gonna start with some songs about barnyard animals.
今天我们要先唱一些 关于农场动物的歌曲
Oh,the cow in the meadow goes "moo"
草地上的牛说哞
Then the farmer hits him And grinds him up
农夫在敲它的头 把它绞成肉酱
And that's how we get hamburgers
汉堡就是这样来的
Now chickens!
现在…鸡
Only you who can save her,Drake!
崔克，你是唯一救得了她的人
Damn it! I'm a doctor. I'm not God!
该死，我是医生，我不是神
There goes my whole belief system.
我的信仰就是这样被推翻了的
It's Erika.
是艾丽
Quick! Shut off the TV.
老天，快，关掉电视
I wanna see what happens!
不，我要看结果
I get Leslie out of the coma then we make out.
我救丝莉脱离昏迷状态 然后我们亲热
How can that be? You were kissing Sabrina!
怎么可能？你刚才亲了莎宾娜
Rachel,it's a world where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
瑞秋，那只是乔伊 是神经外科医生的世界
Hey,Erika. Come in.
艾丽，请进
How did you get here so fast? I just saw you in Salem.
你怎么这么快就到了？ 我刚刚还在沙仑看到你
Right,they choppered me in.
对，他们用…直升机送我
What's up?
什么事？
You're having a little party too!
还有一场小派对
-ls she here? -Who?
她在吗？ 谁啊？
Sabrina. I know about you two!
莎宾娜，你们的事我全知道了
I saw you today,kissing in the doctor's lounge.
我看到你们两个 在医生休息室里接吻
It's not what you think
不是你想的那样子啦，那是…
You told me I was the only one!
你说你心里只有我
All right,look. That's it.
好，听着，够了
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
我想我们不该再见面了
I should have told you a long time ago...
我知道我很久以前 就应该告诉你了…
... but I am not Drake Ramoray.
…我并不是雷崔克医生
I'm not even a doctor. I'm an actor. I just pretend to be a doctor.
我连医生都不是，我是个演员 我只是假装我是医生而已
Oh,my God! Do the people at the hospital know?
天哪，那医院的人 知道这件事情吗？
Somebody wanna help me out here?
你们谁来帮帮忙，好不好？
Oh,I know! I know!
我知道…
Where am I?
我在哪里？
University Hospital...
大学的附设医院…
... where you've been for the last 18 years.
…你已经在这里度过十八年了
How can you be here and there?
你怎么会在两个地方？
Because it's a TV show!
因为那是电视节目
What are you getting at?
崔克，你到底要说什么？
I'm not Drake!
我不是崔克
That's right! He's not Drake. He's...
没错 他不是崔克，他是…
... Hans Ramoray,Drake's evil twin!
…雷汉斯，崔克邪恶的双胞胎
Is this true?
真的吗？
Yes! Yes,it is true!
是真的
And I know this...
我知道因为…
... because he pretended to be Drake to sleep with me!
…他假装他是崔克 来…来骗我上床
And then he told me he would run away with me!
然后他告诉我他要带我私奔
And he didn't!
他骗我
And you left the toilet seat up, you bastard!
然后你马桶盖没有放下来 你这个浑蛋
Is all this true?
这些都是真的吗？
Yes,I'm afraid it is.
是，恐怕是真的了
You deserve much better than me.
我根本配不上你，艾丽
You deserve to be with the real Drake. He's the one you fell in love with.
你应该跟真正的崔克在一起 你爱上的人是他
Go to Salem. Find him!
去沙仑吧，去找他
He's the guy for you!
他才是你的王子
Oh,Hans!
汉斯
Hans?
汉斯？
Hans!
汉斯！
Yo,evil twin!
邪恶的双胞胎
Right. Goodbye,Erika.
对，再见，艾丽
Good luck in Salem.
一切顺利
Take care.
保重了
I'll never forget you,Hans.
我永远不会忘记你的
All right. The people who threw the water!
刚才是谁向我泼水！
Helping you out!
我们只是想帮你
Fired?
开除？
Why?
为什么？
The library board got a lot of complaints from parents...
有很多父母向图书馆的 董事会投诉…
...about the stuff in your songs.
…你歌词里的一些内容有问题
I can't believe it!
我真不敢相信
Did you tell your board that the kids want to hear the truth?
难道说你没有告诉你的董事会 孩子们多么想听实话吗？
I see.
我懂了
Maybe if you just played some regular kiddy songs?
或许如果你只是唱一些 一般的儿歌
What do you want me to be? Like some...
不，你要…我当什么呢？
...stupid,big, like,purple dinosaur?
…当一只愚蠢的 紫色大恐龙吗？
You don't have to be Barney.
我又没说你必须当巴尼
Who's Barney?
巴尼是谁啊？
I tracked down Marcel and get this. He's healthy,he's happy...
我是追查马赛追查到这个的 现在它很健康也很快乐…
...and he's in New York filming Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
…它在纽约拍“危机总动员二 病毒肆虐曼哈顿”
You're kidding!
你骗人
-This is amazing! -I know.
简直妙绝 我知道
I finally get a part on TV, and the monkey's making movies.
我才终于混上电视 这猴子开始拍电影了
Rachel,I'm ready.
瑞秋，我好了
Excuse me. Is this where the singing lady is,who tells the truth?
抱歉，这是那个 说实话的唱歌小姐吗？
I guess that's me.
对呀，我猜那就是我
She's here!
她在这里
Sometimes men love women
有时男人爱女人
Sometimes men love men
有时男人爱男人
Then there are bisexuals
然后还有双性恋
Though some just say They're kidding themselves
虽然有些说他们在骗自己
This is exciting! I haven't seen my monkey in a year.
真是令人兴奋 我都快一年没见到我的猴子了
What,you never look down in the shower?
你洗澡从来不往下看吗？
I'm not allowed to make one joke in the "monkey is penis" genre?
我连说个“猴子等于 命根子”的笑话都不可以吗？
Back up,please.
好了，好了
Back up. Come on.
各位，往后退
Excuse me. Where can we find the monkey?
打扰了 那只猴子在什么地方？
I'm sorry. It's a closed set.
抱歉，各位 这场戏不对外开放
I'm sorry,you don't understand. I'm a friend of his.
对不起，你不了解 我…我是它的朋友
We used to live together.
我们…我们以前住在一起的
And I have a time share in the Poconos with Flipper.
是啊，我跟海豚飞宝 还在波可若分租公寓过呢
There he is!
罗斯，它在那里
Hey! Buddy!
兄弟
Marcel! Marcel!
马赛…
In the jungle
在丛林里
The mighty jungle
偌大的丛林
The lion sleeps tonight
今夜狮子睡着了
In the jungle The mighty jungle
在丛林里，偌大的丛林
The lion sleeps tonight
今夜狮子睡着了
They won't take you to the vet
他们不带你去看兽医
You're obviously not Their favorite pet
你显然不是最受宠的宠物
Smelly cat Smelly cat
臭臭猫，臭臭猫
It's not your fault
那不是你的错
-What? -I'm sorry.
怎么了？ 对不起
What's wrong with that?
那有什么不对吗？
You might want to pick a more masculine note.
我想你应该选择一个 男性化一点的调子比较好